Dustin Bosveld

(970)430-8039 - DustinBosveld@gmail.com

Profile:

«««< HEAD I'm passionate about: excellence, learning, and launching people to reach their full potential (leadership). Quite a long time ago, I was thinking about the phrase 'work smarter, not harder'. I decided it was a better idea to adopt the approach of 'work smarter and harder'. I will not half do a job and I intend on getting things right the first time, or learn how to do things correctly the next time I'm in a similar situation. I enjoy taking on challenging projects to expand my skill set. I also really like solving problems. Additionally, I have a really good memory and can remember nearly everything I learn. I spent over three years learning how to effictively lead people and have actively been in a leadership role on the job since June 2017. By doing things in excellence and developing people I intend to change the world around me.

Experience:

Team Lead: RGIS, March 2017 - Present

• Effectively lead teams of 3-50 people in providing accurate and efficient inventory service

•

Diligently work of provide reliable inventory figures to clients

I'm passionate about: excellence, learning, and launching people to reach their full potential. I will not half do a job and I insist on doing things right the first time. I am constantly learning new skills. And, most importantly, I constantly work to promote people to their full potential.

Experience:

Inventory Supervisor: RGIS, March 2017 - Present

- Lead inventory crews deliver accurate and efficent inventories
- Prepare for inventories through direct communication with customers
- Produce reports on inventories with high accuracy and efficiently

Youth Leader: Rez.church January 2017 - Present

- Mentor and lead groups middle school students
- Prepare and deliver relevant messages to students »»»> 6779443... Update resume

Mail Shop Clerk: Front Range Enterprises and Communication, February 2015 - October 2016

- Produce bulk mail by operating specialized equipment
- Troubleshoot and repair bulk mail machines
- Drive finalized bulk mail to the post office

Customer Service Representative: Qualfon, August 2012 - February 2015

- Answer L1 Technical support calls for TiVo
- Troubleshoot TiVo devices in a timely manner
- Assist customers

Technology Intern: Eaton School District Re2, August 2010 - May 2012

- Troubleshoot and repair faulty computers
- Perform software installations and upgrades on production machines
- Image around 1000 computers for deployment
- Run network cables
- Manage Linux installations

Education:

- Leadership school: RSM, 3 years training
- Technical school: Front Range Community College, Network+ and A+ Certification courses
- High School: Eaton High School, Graduate

Job Skills:

- Proficient at leading groups of people
- Able to follow instructions
- Adaptable
- Good at optimizing workflows
- $\bullet~$ I enjoy learning new things
- Proficient at typing
- Exceptional memory
- Troubleshooting

References:

Greg Brown, Leadership school director and mentor: (720) 442-2348

Andrea Leonard, Current employer: (918) 805-7195

Isaiah Hupp, Pastor: (970) 573-8186